Trade Union Archives Series Two, part 1 & 2 on Microfilm 6078 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Trade Union Archives Series Two, part 1 & 2 on Microfilm
1885- 1941
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Association of Card and Blowing Room Operatives
Amalgamated Weavers' Association
6078 mf
2.89 cubic feet
26 microfilm reels
Microfilm.
9279625
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 23, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Scope and Contents
Part One: Minutes and Reports of the Amalgamated Association of Card and Blowing Room Operatives, 188-1940. Part Two: General Council and Central Committee Minutes of the Amalgamated Weavers' Association 1885- 1941.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Textile workers--Labor unions--Great Britain--History.; Amalgamated Weavers' Association x Archives.; Amalgamated Association of Card and Blowing Room Operatives --Archives.
9279625
- Jan. 1888-Dec. 1905-Part 1 (Reel 1)
- Volumes 4-5 -- Jun. 1893-Dec.1897-Part 1 (Reel 2)
- Volumes 6-7 -- Jan. 1896-Dec. 1905-Part 1 (Reel 3)
- Volumes 8-9 -- Jan. 1900-Dec. 1904-Part 1 (Reel 4)
- Volumes 10-11 -- Jan. 1905-Dec.1912-Part 1 (Reel 5)
- Volumes 12-13 -- Jan. 1906-Dec. 1916-Part 1 (Reel 6)
- Volume 14 -- Jan. 1917-Dec. 1920-Part 1 (Reel 7)
- Volume 15 -- Jan. 1921-Dec. 1924-Part 1 (Reel 8)
- Volume 16 -- Jan. 1925-Dec. 1929-Part 1 (Reel 9)
- Volume 17 -- Jan. 1930-Oct. 1935-Part 1 (Reel 10)
- Volume 18 -- Jan. 1936-Dec. 1940-Part 1 (Reel 11)
- General Council Minutes - Part 2: Volume 1 - Annual Reports - 1885-1910 (Reel 12)
- General Council Minutes - Part 2: Volumes 4-5 -- June 24, 1888-Nov. 16, 1895 (Reel 13)
- General Council Minutes - Part 2: Volumes 6-7 -- June 15, 1895-June 17, 1905 (Reel 14)
- General Council Minutes -- Part 2: Volumes 8-10 - Sept. 23, 1905-Dec. 6, 1919 (Reel 15)
- General Council Minutes -- Part 2: Volume 11-13 - Jan. 10, 1920-Jun. 11, 1932 (Reel 16)
- General Council Minutes - Part 2: Volumes 14-16 - June 18, 1932-Dec. 21, 1940 (Reel 17)
- Central Committee Minutes - Part 2: July 21, 1902-May 14, 1906 (Reel 18)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Dec. 15, 1911-Sep. 11, 1918 (Reel 19)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Sept. 19, 1918-Sept. 4, 1925 (Reel 20)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Sept. 15, 1925-June 24, 1929 (Reel 21)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: June 28, 1929-Aug. 20, 1932 (Reel 22)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Aug. 25, 1932-Nov. 13, 1936 (Reel 23)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Nov. 20, 1936-Jan. 18, 1938 (Reel 24)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Jan. 18, 1938 (cont.)-Aug. 18, 1939 (Reel 25)
- Central Committee Minutes -- Part 2: Aug. 19, 1939-Mar. 28, 1941 (Reel 26)